[music]
>> In this release, we are adding a new
quality management extension. So, now
you can install it and comply with the
regulatory requirements and the industry
standards. And of course, you can use it
during receiving of goods or checking
the produced output
and ensure that quality is right as
internally, but also to make sure that
your customer happy with the quality
items you are shipping.
So, now with a quality management
extension, you can trigger
tests automatically when something
happens in the system. You don't need to
worry about it. You can schedule them to
do them on recurring basis.
For example, if you need from time to
time recheck goods which
usually reducing the quality over the
time.
And you can trigger the inspection
manually just because you receive some
input from outside or internal sources
that something is not really good and
you better to stop and check.
And it's
super flexible solution actually because
many companies use different business
practices and quality process can be
very very different in each
industry or organization or even for
each vendors or product groups.
It's very easy to configure.
And it might happen from time to time
that as a result of the quality check
you discover that some items are
non-compliant. What to do? There are
different options which automate
handling of non-compliant items in the
Business Central.
But enough of these the slides.
Let's take a look at the demo. How it
actually works.
I'm in the Business Manager Role Center
doing my normal job buying stuff. Let's
go to purchase, purchase orders.
I already created purchase order up
front. It contains some coffee beans.
It's a item tracking
items with a lot. And what I will do as
usually, I just post receipt.
You can notice the new
notification appears in
notifying me that new inspection was
created.
Normally, when you implement quality
management in the real life, you don't
need to display this notification to the
person who is a performing
uh posting of
orders, receipt, transfers, maybe output
because inspections are not for them.
It's for
other people who will be performing
quality. But during demonstration, it's
very convenient when we see that quality
inspection is created and we can jump to
it directly from the
relevant document. So, I posted receipt
and my inspection was created
automatically.
I can see that I'm uh
checking
uh quality of roasted beans. I can see
item number. I can see lot information
because yes, this item requires item
tracking for lots with expiration dates
and I assigned something already in the
my purchase document up front. You can
also see the quality quantity, but if I
will scroll down
I can see a list of different tests I
need to perform. Let's expand it
and do them. Notice, I will be
populating the test value column
and
what will happen?
So, the first one, I press the assist
edit and I can see pop-up page which
allows me to select
one out of three options.
And the package in my case looks
undamaged
which is a good sign, good starting
point.
Labeling, correct and readable? Yes. Oh,
again pop-up window, but looks slightly
different. Yeah, it has two options.
Yes.
will be yes.
Then the next one
bean defect types.
Again, I can choose something from the
list including the blank option.
But this time something is not good. The
color of the coffee beans
looks suspicious.
Let's mark it.
Uh what about form?
Kind of mixed.
But it still passed. Interesting.
And that what about moisture? Now I'm
using some equipment to check the
moisture. And it will be right in the
middle
of what? Of the past description. You
can see that I have past and failed
descriptions which provide me some hints
about what do I need to enter to make
sure that it's
clarified classified as a past or
failed.
I can provide some additional comments
or I can provide comments for each line.
There is a special note column where I
can provide more details for each
individual test I'm performing.
All right, most of them
passed, one failed. One failure is
already enough
to
to mark the whole inspection as failed.
So, you can see the result says fail.
I'm ready to finish my inspection, but
before that, let's also attach the
image. So, to to document how it looks
like. If I'm using device, I can take a
picture right from it, but
I'm using laptop, so I will just drag
and drop the image prepared up front.
Yeah.
Color looks suspicious.
All right, now we are ready to change
status to
of the whole inspection to finish.
So, now it documented the process. Hey,
I finished my inspection, but again
something happened automatically. The
system created transfer order.
Do I want to open it? Of course, I want.
We are doing the demonstration here.
So, transfer order was created
automatically and it transferring
quantity
three
from main to east location. Why three?
You can ask.
And before you do that
we can also double check that
lot information is passed correctly. Lot
information is passed. And now the time
to answer the question why three.
Because even if I received 25, I decided
not to test all of them. I decided to
test only some.
Smaller sample size and I have extra
field sample size which is defined as
three.
All right, more questions more
questions, but
we will find answers later.
Right now we done with our inspection.
And what we will do next, we will close
this purchase document and move to a
different role. So, now it will be sales
process.
We also have a sales document prepared
up front
with a
the same item. Now we need to
specify item tracking details.
Uh
select something from the list.
Good.
So, we are ready to ship 10 items. Let's
try.
Post and ship.
We cannot. We can see some red letters
which says that my transaction my sales
transaction was blocked because there is
inspection
with a result fail
for this specific lot of this item and
we do not allow sales transactions.
So, what do we do next?
Maybe it's a good idea not to sell items
which has indication that they are not
of the good quality.
All right, what do we do next?
Let's go to the Role Center.
We find here quality
inspections
and uh
find our inspection
and we will recreate it.
Let's try it again. So, we do the
another check.
We open this new inspection.
Probably this time we will take a look
at the remaining quantity. So, we
already uh
moved three out. So, now we going to
test all of them.
So, we are doing another test.
And again, packaging looks good.
This time
color is actually fine.
So, that was a
fine.
And no other other
signals of the better or defect types in
the in the coffee beans.
And they are looks very good. They all
the same and um
moisture is the same. So, probably we
were unlucky when we picked the three
different samples.
So, they were
not good. But the remaining ones looks
looks fine and we again ready to finish
this inspection.
Yes, we finishing it.
What else can we do?
We can actually print it.
There are three documents. Certificate
of analysis.
Let's take a look at the layouts. We are
in the progress of changing layout. So,
when you will see this video, I would
expect you to see a very different
layout. But the idea and the data set
will stay the same.
All right.
So, this is external facing document
which we can attach to the document and
communicate externally. So, we see
information about
what we tested,
who we tested,
and then information the results if it's
passed or failed situation and
information about conditions.
We also have a non-conformance report.
Where we can see
the same information but with a slightly
different details. You can see that for
each test we performed packaging,
labeling, coffee bean defects, etc. We
have information about who registered
it. It's a username. Yeah, this is a
my name apparently in this environment
and the date time when the test was
performed.
All right.
So,
now we
completed the quality check
and now it is a passed. Let's go back to
our sales document and try to complete
the transaction again. Let's try to ship
to ship these goods to our customers.
And perfectly, goods were shipped to the
customers and we know that quality of
these goods were very good.
We checked it
and we documented the fact.
All right.
Let's stop and
think how we achieved it. Like what
actually happened.
If you're not ready for details, you can
stop watching this video now, but
otherwise,
let's switch to a different role center.
With a quality management extension, we
also including the special quality
management role center.
I don't think many people will use it by
default, but it has one very valuable
part, demo tools.
If I will activate show demo tools, you
can see the number of steps
which will guide you through the setup
process and help you to understand how
to configure and use the product.
So, if you forgot how to use it, instead
of watching video, you can always jump
to the quality management role center
and explore the tools. So, the first
step is about demo data.
Ex- the demo data, we do not need to
actually set up data. Set up data are
installed automatically with extension,
but it is very much isolated, so no
impact on any other stuff
or functionality of the product. So,
it's a very safe to install. The only
things which will you see is number
series.
One number series series.
Otherwise, for demonstration purposes,
you might want to get some sample data
like test, etc.
For this one, you install
stuff in the quality
install quality
uh
module
with the Contoso app.
Contoso demo tool
and you can see quality management
already installed, so now we see all the
data. That's good.
The next one,
inspection results. You can ask like why
why why are we starting with results?
Uh because actually we are not
inspecting results.
It is
results configuration, so we need to
configure possible outcomes. What does
it mean?
By default, there are three different
states,
inspection not started or in progress
and then failed or passed.
But sometimes, the world is not black
and white. It has like shadows in the
between.
For example, in the school, you have
multiple grades.
And uh
you can always add extra grades to and
and the register the fact that something
perfectly passed and something like
almost failed, but they still good. It
is possible, but by default and many
companies probably will be happy with
it, we have three statuses.
What else do we see here?
Evaluation sequence. That's very
interesting
because
it impacts on which status will be
applied.
You will see
a bit later.
Another one interesting field, result
visibility. It says promoted
or configuration only.
So, promoted, it means it will be
visible in many places. For example, in
the
inspection or printed in the document.
We saw it. And the last one, but not
least,
it's a group of different allow columns
which instruct what to do if there are
items
in if there are inspections
for specific item with specific item
tracking or lot tracking information.
So, you saw the error when I tried to
post the document because system
identified that there is an item with a
lot 25 which has inspection in failed
status.
Remember the word failed? And
regarding sales, it is not allowed. So,
the sales transaction was blocked.
But we allow every other transactions.
Maybe it would be reasonable also to
block consumption
uh if you in some manufacturing
scenarios.
All right.
Too much for the beginning? The next one
will be easier.
Or not.
Uh quality tests.
So,
everybody different, so we do the
different checks. In some cases, we need
to measure temperature. In some cases,
we need to measure sizes or basically we
can measure sizes
for different group of items. Then
you define all these quality parameters.
All different type of those.
And they kind of
work as a fields, so you can
have them in different types.
Decimals, integer, Boolean, looks
familiar, test, date,
option and table look up.
That's something to explore. But let's
start with the simple cases.
For example, we will pick
moisture which we already explored. So,
the name and description
uh [snorts]
easy to do. Then test value type.
It is integer in my case, but makes
sense to have a decimal if it can be
some decimal points.
All right.
Then we can define allowable values.
It's percentage, so it makes sense to do
like between 0 and 100. So, we do not
allow inspector
to make a typo and enter, for example,
1,000. So, the system just do not accept
does not accept this value. So, value
must be between 0 and 100.
But again, looks very familiar to the
uh Business Central uh filtering
capability, so nothing prevents you from
doing something like that which makes no
sense from uh
percentage, but makes total sense from
the filtering
possibilities.
You can always learn
about filters
in the documentation.
But all right, let me remove this
strange filter string
and go backwards.
Another one, default value. You can
actually
save some effort and specify what value
will be populated by default. It is good
and bad. On one hand,
user, the inspector, do not
does not need to modify the value when
doing inspections. So, like, yeah, all
good all good all good, match, pass.
But because they do not change the value
in the lines, system will not register
who actually
check this specific line. So, if you
want to register the fact that somebody
actually
checked specific test or performed
specific test and know the time when it
happened and the name or who performed
it,
you
should not use default values because
otherwise lines will not be updated.
Good to know, but let's move forward.
Result conditions. This is very
interesting tab. It allows you to
specify what actually we are
checking
and what will be
uh the results of how the output will be
evaluated.
All right. What we know?
What we know? We know that we decided
that we have only two buckets in
addition to in progress, pass and fail.
And this is a pass condition and this is
a fail condition. So, here we can
specify even if we allow user to enter
something between 0 and 100,
the good values will be
between 10 and 12.
What if user enters
three?
Then it is outside of this range, but
within each each range. Yeah, it's
definitely in the fail condition. So,
three is definitely not zero, so yeah,
fail is applicable.
And it's not applicable and it's not
here.
So, system will decide.
What if somebody enters 11?
Then,
surprisingly, both pass and fail
conditions applied.
Yeah, because 11 is definitely not
equal zero,
so it is fail.
But it is also
between 10 and 12 which we decided to to
use as a pass condition.
So, which one system will pick?
And here we need to
check results.
Quality inspection results.
Remember, fail and pass and there is
something which is called evaluation
sequence. So, system will first
check fail condition. Yeah, it failed
because 11 is not equal zero as we
decide.
Failed.
Shall we check further? Yes, we should.
And let's check the pass condition.
But 11 is also between 20 and 12. So,
pass and because it has a high
evaluation sequence and applicable, so
it wins.
That's might be difficult. So, that's
why up to you how you define this these
different conditions. Maybe you can just
write something absolutely different
like
till nine or
what is 12?
That's more reasonable.
And then you don't need to think about
these prioritizations. Up to you. Again,
flexible,
powerful,
a bit difficult.
Let's take a look at another example.
Decimal we don't want to explore right
now because
kind of the same, but what about
Boolean?
Here we have example about break checks
breaks check. So, this is
you can always generate a checklist when
people just say like yes, I tested this
this this this this and set
checkbox.
Boolean field is very good for it. And
you have pass and fail conditions which
are very
clearly defined.
You can define the default value.
And let me press the button.
And this is how it will look for for
user. So, we can don't need to type in
information. We can always select from
possible
possible options.
All right. So, this is like very short
list with only two values.
Now we're talking about list.
List.
For people who
developed and used C L O L as a
developer know the word option.
It's a data type which allows you to set
to provide number of allowed values and
separate them with a comma. So, this is
exactly what I did. I specified
option type,
but which value user can select from?
They are all listed in allowable values
field.
And it's color for etc. etc. And I put
the
beginning
I have it as as an empty string. Maybe
that was not very smart. Maybe
I should have something
like
no defect.
Maybe that looks even even better.
That's that's a not a not a bad option.
All right.
And this is my pass conditions like all
of them.
And
now I have no defects. Maybe I could
specify it differently.
I can open this quality inspection
template edit and use it.
Or I can just type my formula directly.
No defects.
Should also work.
Yeah, I'm using it in already different
template and inspection. So, of course
if I'm doing some changes,
it should be propagated.
Good.
Is it the only way to define multiple
selection?
Not really. And you already guess that
I'm going to talk about something which
is called lookup table lookup.
Coffee bean uniformity. That's our
option. I select table lookup and then
finally the table lookup configuration
first up start making sense. So, here we
are defining what kind of lookup you
want to do. So, we can do lookup to any
table in Business Central. Yeah, really.
Let's try to do that. For example, it
will be
country.
Country.
And it will be table lookup table
lookup.
>> [snorts]
>> And then
I'm going to use country.
Do you remember the ID?
Let me guess. Probably it will be nine.
Not that one.
All right. Now I can select any value
from country.
Let me let me show.
Looks empty. Why so?
So, it should have some values. We
definitely have a list information about
country because I did not specify which
field I want to use.
Notice it's not using primary key
because again we can select any table
with a very complex primary key which
consists of like two, three,
five in some cases
fields.
So, we need to pick something else.
Which field I'm going to use?
I will be using name.
All right.
And you can see allowable allowable
values automatically populated. And if I
will click here, I can see the list.
Yeah, names.
But
I can also apply some filters. For
example, I'm only interested in
countries
where
Let's focus on European ones.
Not empty.
Why not?
And now the list
is shorter and looks like it includes
only European countries.
All right. What if I will do some crazy
stuff here?
What if I will go to
GL entries.
And I will be looking at
No, I'm not using any filters. That's on
purpose. And I'm selecting the entry
number.
All right. What will happen if I will
try to click here?
Million of entries?
Definitely not. As you can see, it
stopped exactly on the number 30.
Why?
Performance reasons, of course, like
because if people select something
unreasonable
and it will take some time to browse
through the all GL ledger entries.
We don't want that. So, there is a setup
in the quality management setup where we
have some setups which actually dictates
the number of rows to fetch in the
lookup. That's a little bit interesting
name of the field, but the value 30
definitely indicate that it's used in
this specific scenario. Let me change it
to 40
and and try it again.
Oh, now it goes up to the 40. Should we
try two millions?
No, not in this demo.
All right.
But what if I don't have the table with
the right data?
We have something for you.
Some
values.
As soon as you define decide to use
table lookup,
the table lookup configuration it gets
automatically populated with a very
specific table. This is its name. This
is its number.
What does this table has in it?
We can always check.
Quality
lookup. Test lookup values.
As you can see, it's a very interesting
table. It has the first
field
which similar to what we see in the
in the quality test names. Yeah, so like
we remember we had something called
coffee defects. Yeah, with a color for
etc.
Oh, no.
Coffee uniformity irregular, mixed, and
uniform. You remember them. So, these
three lines are linked to specific test
by the lookup code. And it happens
automatically as soon as you define the
the new test. You can see that lookup
field filter is populated.
It says that lookup group code to be
used some values in this case. Okay, not
bad. And lookup field is automatically
populated the value.
Now I need to somehow populate the
values. The easiest way will be
go to allowable values and press the
button.
So, that's a super easy way to
initialize this table. We can of course
go to a separate uh
quality test lookup table as we saw few
seconds earlier,
but this is just easier.
Value one,
value two,
value three.
Okay.
And it already works. I can already
select the the default value and in the
the same way it will be selected in the
inspection as well.
All right.
Phew.
I promised to
make this easier.
I think it is
now
after this video.
All right. So, what what we learned so
far? You have quality inspection results
where you can define fail or pass or
maybe more.
And then you can instruct which of those
should be propagated to the test and use
them. All right. Now we define the test
of different type integer or decimal or
maybe date or maybe text or maybe
something else.
Option lookup and Boolean for different
type of selections.
All right. But now time to take the
right test
and gather them together.
And it will be quality template.
We have collection of different
templates and
the one which we already
saw, it's a coffee related coffee bean
templates.
I have multiple different tests added as
a lines. So, that's exactly what I want
to check. You remember we checked the
package visual labels
uh
some coffee parameters even additional
comments, free entry text.
What we didn't check is the
verification. It's a special
entry of type label.
Does nothing only just to split stuff
and uh looks look good on when you print
the document when you print the
inspection. It's a it works as a
separator.
All right, separator with name.
If you can enter.
Also, remember about sampling size. We
have two types
in addition to to not define
uh sample size. We have two types, fixed
quantity and percent of quantity. So, I
decided to go with a percent, 10%. What
will be 10% of 25?
2.5, round it up, three.
So, only only uh
integers are allowed here.
All right, so now we know what to test.
We know how many
what is a what is a samples quantity.
How do we connect this template
to specific operation?
Again,
it's called inspection generation rules.
What is it? It's a separate table which
defines
when this template can be used.
And for what?
So, this template
I decided to use it for purchase
scenarios.
Can I use it for something else?
Definitely. For example, I can use it
for
sales scenario. What? Sales return.
Yeah, of course.
Sales scenarios when we are receiving
something, it is sales return.
But, when
is it like for every line?
You can define conditions. You can
define conditions for line. I decided
that I'm only running this inspection if
my location is main. But, I can have
other parameters, maybe quantity.
Maybe maybe
any of other hundred of fields we have
here. For example, I can skip drop
shipments. We have a separate video
about drop shipments, by the way.
All right.
Then, I can also enhance my filters and
deal with
items.
Even if
location is main, let's check the items.
I decided only to test items where item
tracking code is not empty. Why?
You can use quality management
for different purposes without tracking
code. But, if you use tracking code,
then
there even more
interesting scenarios. For example,
uh they all limitations which we saw in
the quality results like allow post,
allow
allow sales, allow purchase, allow allow
consumption, etc. They only work for
items with item tracking.
For items without tracking, you need to
use a different ways to to block them
and exclude them from inventory if they
are
of not good quality.
All right, and items also have concept
of attributes. So, we can also define
extra parameters about attributes.
The next one
is when do we
create inspection? Maybe manually.
Fair enough, you can press the button in
which is available in many many places.
In the purchase document, item
trackings, you can press the buttons.
Or it might happen automatically for
different
intent, is it purchase or sales? Of
course, the event or trigger will be
also different. For example, for
purchase orders, it can be order
received or order is released.
It's not applicable for sales returns.
For sales returns, we have a separate
column which kind of
very similar. Something is received.
Good.
Scheduled group is if for inspections
which you want to run on the recurring
basis and use a job queue to create
them. So, it's a not
business events, it's timer based event.
All right, so we defined this
uh
inspection generation rule.
And now, as soon as we post purchase
document, inspection will be created.
So, this is our existing inspections.
Now, they look dramatically more
familiar to you. So, we see information
about tracking. So, what exactly we're
testing. Remember it.
The sample size.
You know where it's coming from? From
the source rules.
The the result. Where is my result?
Okay, this is my result in the status.
And you know where results is coming
from? From the quality inspection
results.
And you remember that it blocks sales
because my item has a
uh item tracking defined. And these
lines are coming from template and in
the template from quality test. And we
can open the them to get additional
information. For example, what does this
pass and fail uh criteria means.
Yeah.
Pass condition, fail condition.
All right.
Almost there. Almost there.
One more page to explore.
It will be quality setup.
Quality management setup.
As I mentioned, once we install this
extension because it will be
preinstalled, but only for new
environments. So, like if you create new
environment in the
Oh, it's 2026 nowadays.
Uh
wave one release,
quality management will be there. So,
you can directly navigate to quality
management setup page
and other places.
And uh
and explore.
But, uh
for existing customers, for existing
customers, what will happen? Uh
you need to navigate in the app source
and find the quality management app and
install it. And at this point of time,
something will happen, system will
initialize
some values. But again, the only table
the normal table uh
or shared table, it will be the number
series. So, with this value will be will
be inserted. Everything else is super
safe. So, unless you suspect that you
will have a conflict with the quality
inspection number series, you're very
safe to install it, uninstall it at any
point of time.
All right.
What else?
What are these fields are doing here?
They are default values. They will be
used in the
when you create generation rules,
quality inspection generation rule.
Remember my purchase trigger, it will
set by to never, but I could set up the
default value. Then, once I initialize a
new line, it will be
purchase trigger will be
initialized
respectively.
Another one.
That's a good one.
Which reminds me that I forgot to show
you something in the quality inspection.
It is about what to do
uh what you can do
with uh failed or passed scenarios.
Let me show it.
Let's navigate to the to some
inspection. For example, the pass one.
And what we can do here?
We can finish it.
You know, we can reopen it.
We can create reinspection. In this
case, it will stay here, but the new
version will be created. And then, you
can do something.
Uh
reopen and deletion is limited by
permission. So, if you are not quality
management administrator,
you cannot do these actions. It's only
only
uh
administrator can do that. Other people
just recreate inspections.
All right.
And then, what you can do? Multiple
actions.
You can move inventory.
What does it mean?
Reclassification journal.
You can move it also using transfer
order.
You can move it inside
by using uh
between bins. Again, reclassification
journal or internal put away if you're
using directed put away and pick
scenarios. Negative adjustment.
Write it off.
It's broken, no chance.
And purchase return order. You can
retry, return it to the vendor. Depends
on your agreements with your vendor.
What else?
We already know.
You can also change item tracking.
Maybe
lot number or expiration dates.
All right, and when you
trigger, for example,
negative adjustment.
You can define
what quantity to use. You can use the
full quantity, you can specify quantity
which you can specify here.
Or you can use sample quantity failed or
pass quantity. You can see that we have
a with a separate field and sample
quantity which is right now hiding is
also available.
Populate some extra fields. For example,
reason code. Yeah, it makes sense to use
a different reason code.
Additional filters and actions. Okay,
the journal line is created. What next?
Nothing.
You can review and post it later maybe
with approvals.
But you can also post it immediately if
you do not use approvals.
All right.
Extra fields.
Do nothing. Cancel.
But you remember
that in my demo scenario that happened
automatically.
The answer is
workflows.
Yes, yes.
The
standard built-in workflows.
We do not have templates because these
workflows are very
simple, I would say.
They are not that complex to configure
as any approval workflows.
When you need to approve one first etc.
No, it's a one liner basically. When
something happens,
when event happened and there are
four quality management related events.
All about inspection. So, quality
inspection created,
changed, finished, reopened. So, there
are four events.
Very simple.
When one of these events happen, you
select which one,
and you can change check condition. It
is finished but with what condition? Or
maybe for which item because you can
decide different rules for different
items. Which location etc.
Result fail, then what do we do?
There again number of default responses.
It's a little bit longer list but again
manageable.
If you're using tracking, you can block
tracking numbers. For example, you start
inspection, you immediately block
tracking numbers. You finish inspection,
you do what?
Depends on the result. Maybe you
unblocked finish status.
Actions. That's a simple
six
responses. Next one is about inspection
itself. You create inspection, you can
recreate inspection, you can finish
inspection.
You can reopen inspection. So, there are
something based on
based on conditions.
So, there are three actions about
inspections itself.
And then about movements. You can move
or whatever you saw.
Negative adjustment,
internal put away, purchase return,
transfer order,
move inventory from inspection,
uh
yeah, maybe something else.
I don't see something don't see anything
else. And tracking information. You can
change check
change tracking information. So, the
same actions which you saw in the
quality inspection itself.
And some people are asking,
"What about Power Automate? Isn't it the
future?"
Power Automate is very great tool and we
do expose the similar events and the
similar responses through API. So, if
you prefer to use Power Automate, go
ahead. But
there is a benefit of using some of
these internally with built-in workflows
because if you when you create
inspection
and you plan to block lot,
there is no point to call the external
engine
and do orchestration outside and then go
back and do market. Like, why? You can
perform these actions very much inside
the Business Central without leaving and
solving all these authentication
problems etc. It's a very simple
activity. So, with simple activities
which do not require
human involvement, maybe it's not
approval notification etc.
And just perform the action.
Do it internally. It's a easy to set up.
It's fast. It runs in the same
transaction. So, if something goes
wrong, it will be rolled back.
I think it has its own list of use cases
and I'm very surprised that we did not
look at it uh
for all 10 years when this workflow
engine was introduced and only focusing
on the approval scenarios. It's actually
very good for simple automation. If
events and response are present. And for
quality management, decent number of
events and decent number of responses
are present. So,
use it.
If you, of course, prefer to
based on some event send notification in
Teams and ask user to make a decision
and then they
choose A or B,
go with it.
APIs, events etc. Everything is exposed.
So,
long video.
We started with a very short and
inspiring demonstration how you can use
quality management app and how it
impacts the flow and involve different
users in the in the process.
Then
we
did a very deep dive
but not on a different
ideas on how to configure the different
templates, rules etc. connected to
different processes and set up automatic
or maybe manual processes.
So,
time for you to explore. Of course, it's
not everything. There are much more
scenarios which I did not describe.
Check our documentation and if you have
any questions, you know where to find
us.
We have YouTube channel and now we have
a Viva Engage
in addition to our LinkedIn
account
where we are always ready to collaborate
and here for your feedback.
Thank you for watching.
Try it and have a nice day.